<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>job &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/tag/job/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:44:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Cloud Solutions Architect</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Job]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google help]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[job]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jon in google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google Remote eligible Apply Note: Google’s hybrid workplace includes remote roles. By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: Remote locations: Canada; Quebec, CA. Qualifications Minimum qualifications: Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, a related engineering field or equivalent practical experience. 3 years of experience [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Google</li><li>Remote eligible</li><li><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/signin?jobId=CiUAL2FckXcGxxjZ0yGKW7byU3zZXUvWhxrqPpeeG-fwQsXVkkLaEjsArqK0BfHi5v87cDIqsL0hf89skPApgZU6UYGAG3WQs3klEJIl0qw8noefNH6yDv4TgiBYAWEEN_8kmg%3D%3D_V2&amp;jobTitle=Cloud+Solutions+Architect&amp;loc=US" target="_blank">Apply</a></li></ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/5c12925417002a545a62f5ef-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-45" width="840" height="630"/></figure>



<p>Note: Google’s hybrid workplace includes remote roles. By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following:<br><br><strong>Remote locations: Canada; Quebec, CA.</strong></p>



<h2>Qualifications</h2>



<p>Minimum qualifications:</p>



<ul><li>Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, a related engineering field or equivalent practical experience.</li><li>3 years of experience working with cloud-native application development, container orchestration, Unix/Linux environments, site reliability engineering, developing software systems, and/or software security.</li></ul>



<p>Preferred qualifications:</p>



<ul><li>Master&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, a related engineering field, or equivalent work experience.</li><li>5 years of experience working with a variety of enterprise and cloud technology systems, designing solutions, or developing business applications.</li><li>Experience with deployment and orchestration technologies (e.g., Terraform, Puppet, Chef, Salt, Ansible, Docker, Kubernetes, Mesos, OpenStack, or Jenkins).</li><li>Experience in the business technology market, and expertise working closely with sales and marketing teams in cloud computing or related technical fields.</li><li>Ability to effectively communicate complex technical concepts to a broad range of audiences.</li></ul>



<h2>About the job</h2>



<p>The Google Cloud Platform team helps customers transform and build what&#8217;s next for their business all with technology built in the cloud. Our products are engineered for security, reliability and scalability, running the full stack from infrastructure to applications to devices and hardware. Our teams are dedicated to helping our customers, developers, small and large businesses, educational institutions, and government agencies see the benefits of our technology come to life. As part of an entrepreneurial team in this rapidly growing business, you will play a key role in understanding the needs of our customers and help shape the future of businesses of all sizes use technology to connect with customers, employees, and partners.</p>



<p>As an in-house Cloud Solutions Architect on the Blueprint Solutions team, you will accelerate customers’ onboarding to the cloud by delivering automated open source solutions and tools. You will represent the customer within the Config and Policy Automation team and work closely with product managers and software engineers daily. You will help customers implement best practices for migrating and develop/publish solutions to help modernize their application infrastructure. This includes solutions to help automate, manage, and handle infrastructure. You will provide direction on how to tailor the mechanisms used to secure and deploy workloads reliably and safely to production.</p>



<p>Google Cloud provides organizations with leading infrastructure, platform capabilities and industry solutions. We deliver enterprise-grade cloud solutions that leverage Google’s cutting-edge technology to help companies operate more efficiently and adapt to changing needs, giving customers a foundation for the future. Customers in more than 150 countries turn to Google Cloud as their trusted partner to solve their most critical business problems.</p>



<h2>Responsibilities</h2>



<ul><li>Build and maintain open source template configurations and automated solutions for deploying products on Google Cloud.</li><li>Create and deliver best practices recommendations, tutorials, blog articles, sample code, and technical presentations.</li><li>Partner closely with product managers and engineers to refine our products by collaborating on roadmaps, design documents, and prototypes.</li><li>Facilitate deep technical discussions with customers, partners, and Googlers, and provide customer and market feedback to Product and Engineering teams to help define product direction.</li></ul>



<p>Google is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and is an affirmative action employer. We are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity or Veteran status. We also consider qualified applicants regardless of criminal histories, consistent with legal requirements. See also&nbsp;<a href="https://careers.google.com/eeo/">Google&#8217;s EEO Policy</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://careers.google.com/jobs/dist/legal/OFCCP_EEO_Post.pdf">EEO is the Law.</a>&nbsp;If you have a disability or special need that requires accommodation, please let us know by completing our&nbsp;<a href="https://goo.gl/forms/aBt6Pu71i1kzpLHe2">Accommodations for Applicants form</a>.</p>



<p>To all recruitment agencies: Google does not accept agency resumes. Please do not forward resumes to our jobs alias, Google employees or any other organization location. Google is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.</p>



<p>for apply click here: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/signin?jobId=CiUAL2FckXcGxxjZ0yGKW7byU3zZXUvWhxrqPpeeG-fwQsXVkkLaEjsArqK0BfHi5v87cDIqsL0hf89skPApgZU6UYGAG3WQs3klEJIl0qw8noefNH6yDv4TgiBYAWEEN_8kmg%3D%3D_V2&amp;jobTitle=Cloud+Solutions+Architect&amp;loc=US" target="_blank">Apply</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>INFOSYS INTERNSHIP</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infosys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infosys Internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[job]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hey learners! Are you looking for some project based Internship then Infosys Springboard is for you. Infosys Springboard Offering Project Internship is for fresher who wants to learn the new technology . In this Program you will assign to variety of internship and you need to make the teams to complete the internship . To [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hey learners! Are you looking for some project based Internship then Infosys Springboard is for you. Infosys Springboard Offering Project Internship is for fresher who wants to learn the new technology . In this Program you will assign to variety of internship and you need to make the teams to complete the internship .</p>



<p>To know more about this read the blog post below.</p>



<h2>About Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship Program</h2>



<p>The Infosys Springboard internship program is an excellent learning opportunity for students/learners who are aspiring professionals to hone their existing skills and transition to global corporate professionals.</p>



<p>Applicants must complete all the courses prescribed in the learning path for the project and score 60% or above in the self-assessment present in the courses.</p>



<p>They must pass the certifications if any prescribed in the learning path for the project. Here are the learning paths for the pre-requisite learning.</p>



<h2>Eligibility Criteria</h2>



<ul><li>Applicants must have passed 12th Standard or equivalent or higher examination from a recognized Board or University and must be pursuing graduation or completed graduation/post-graduation</li><li>Applicants must complete all the courses prescribed in the pre-requisite learning microsite for the project and score 60% or above in self-assessment present at the end of the course</li><li>They must pass the certification(s) if prescribed in the pre-requisite learning microsite</li><li>They must submit responses to a survey which will be activated when they click on the ‘Apply’ button</li></ul>



<h2>Selection criteria</h2>



<ul><li>The internship with Infosys Springboard will have limited seats</li><li>The following are the guidelines(not limited to) for selection to the program:<ul><li>Completion of courses in the pre-requisite learning microsite and performance in the self-assessments</li><li>Completion of certifications(if any) and performance in them</li><li>Survey responses</li><li>Performance in the interviews with mentors</li><li>Performance in a qualification exam if Infosys decides to conduct one</li><li>The decision of Infosys will be final for selection of interns</li></ul></li></ul>



<h2>Internship Timeline</h2>



<p><strong>Dec 24, 2021</strong></p>



<ul><li>Infosys Springboard Internship opens</li></ul>



<p><strong>Dec 24, 2021 – Jan 14, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Browse for open projects and explore</li><li>Apply for project that suits</li><li>Complete the pre-requisite learning courses and certification(if any)</li><li>Prepare for interview by Project Mentors(if invited)</li></ul>



<p><strong>Jan 17 – 28, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Attend interviews as per shared schedule</li><li>Allocation of project(if selected)</li></ul>



<p><strong>Feb – Apr, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Interact with Project Mentors</li><li>Design, code and test the solution</li><li>Deploy and integrate</li></ul>



<p><strong>Mar – Apr, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Project milestone and evaluations</li></ul>



<h2>List of Projects and other details</h2>



<p>1 : EasyQ – AI Based question &amp; answer generation tool</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL</li><li>Event Intern</li></ul>



<p>2. Event Management</p>



<ul><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>3. GAN for CVD</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: AI and ML</li></ul>



<p>4. HONQPGen – AI Based question hands on generation tool</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Artificial Intelligence</li></ul>



<p>5. InfyDataQ – From Messy to Clean Data</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Open systems</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: LAMP</li></ul>



<p>6. InfyKiddoFun – Making Learning Fun!Theme: Digital Learning</p>



<ul><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, .NET</li></ul>



<p>7. Linux Enterprise Lab – A hands-on experience!</p>



<ul><li>Theme: System Administration</li><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 10 weeks</li><li>Technology: CentOS Everything iso, Ngnix binary</li></ul>



<p>8. Market analyst</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 2</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>9. MeridianPlatform – Outlook plugin integration</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Remote team collaboration</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 10 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL</li></ul>



<p>10. QuestBank – To create a treasure trove of questions for assessments</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Digital Learning</li><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, .NET</li></ul>



<p>11. Brand Management Intern</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>12. Content Marketing Intern</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Content Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 2</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<h3>How to Apply for Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship Program?</h3>



<p>To apply in this Internship&nbsp;<a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://infyspringboard.onwingspan.com/en/page/embed-internship" target="_blank">CLICK HERE</a></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
