<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ravi &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/author/ravi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Jersey</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/jersey/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/jersey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 10:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chadighr kre aashiqi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jercy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rrr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Genre:&#160;Drama,&#160;SportsRelease Date:&#160;31st December, 2021 Cast:&#160;Shahid Kapoor, Mrunal Thakur, Pankaj Kapur Writer/Director:&#160;Gowtam Tinnanauri Producer/s:&#160;Aman Gill, Dil Raju, S. Naga]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2021/01/jersey-001.jpg" alt="" width="359" height="513" title=""/></figure>



<p><strong>Genre:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.koimoi.com/genre/drama/">Drama</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/genre/sports/">Sports</a><br><strong>Release Date:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.koimoi.com/release-date/2021-12-31/">31st December, 2021</a></p>



<p><strong>Cast:</strong>&nbsp;Shahid Kapoor, Mrunal Thakur, Pankaj Kapur</p>



<p><strong>Writer/Director:</strong>&nbsp;Gowtam Tinnanauri</p>



<p><strong>Producer/s:</strong>&nbsp;Aman Gill, Dil Raju, S. Naga Vamshi</p>



<p><strong>Plot:</strong><br>Jersey Review</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_865405"><img src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2021/12/ayushmann-khurrana-vaani-kapoors-chandigarh-kare-aashiqui-box-office-review-is-out-001.jpg" alt="Ayushmann Khurrana &amp; Vaani Kapoor's Chandigarh Kare Aashiqui Box Office Review Is Out" class="wp-image-865405"/><figcaption>Here’s How Much Chandigarh Kare Aashiqui Might Earn ( Photo Credit – Song Still )</figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>Star cast:</strong>&nbsp;Ayushmann Khurrana, Vaani Kapoor, Gourav Sharma, Gautam Sharma &amp; others</p>



<p><strong>Director:</strong>&nbsp;Abhishek Kapoor</p>



<p><strong>Producers:</strong>&nbsp;Bhushan Kumar, Pragya Kapoor, Krishan Kumar &amp; Abhishek Nayyar</p>



<p><strong>Chandigarh Kare Aashiqui Box Office Review: Expectations</strong></p>



<p>It’s an Ayushmann Khurrana film, so expect something niche yet interesting! This line summed up my thought when the trailer was out. Giving more hope was director Abhishek Kapoor’s name attached.</p>



<p>The trailer and the promotional follow-up made it clear that the film isn’t a regular rom-com, especially with a base of trans love story shouldering it. As we have seen in the past, Abhishek Kapoor has delivered some refreshingly entertaining films which have even clicked commercially. And now, with&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/reviews/chandigarh-kare-aashiqui-movie-review-ayushmann-khurrana-vaani-kapoors-beautiful-way-of-saying-normal-di-maa-di/">Ayushmann</a>&nbsp;joining the force, the package looked like a complete winner.</p>



<h1>RRR</h1>



<p>By&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/author/koimoi-com-team-2/">Koimoi.com Team</a>&nbsp;-April 4, 2019Rrr Plot</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2019/04/rrr-3.jpg" alt="RRR" title="RRR"/></figure>



<p><strong>Genre:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.koimoi.com/genre/drama/">Drama</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/genre/period/">Period</a><br><strong>Release Date:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.koimoi.com/release-date/2022-01-07/">07th January, 2022</a></p>



<p><strong>Cast:</strong>&nbsp;N. T. Rama Rao Jr., Ram Charan, Alia Bhatt, Ajay Devgn, Daisy Edgar-Jones</p>



<p><strong>Director:</strong>&nbsp;S.S. Rajamouli</p>



<p><strong>Writer:</strong>&nbsp;V. Vijayendra Prasad</p>



<p><strong>Plot:</strong>&nbsp;RRR is a fictional story of what could have happened in the lives of Alluri Seetharama Raju and Komaram Bheem in those years when they had disappeared. The film stars Jr. NTR &amp; Ram Charan in the lead roles.<br>Rrr Review</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_865423"><img src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2021/12/check-out-rrr-trailer-review-starring-jr-ntr-ram-charan-002.jpg" alt="Check Out RRR Trailer Review Starring Jr NTR &amp; Ram Charan" class="wp-image-865423"/><figcaption>Check Out RRR Trailer Review ( Photo Credit – Still From Trailer )</figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>RRR Trailer Review:</strong>&nbsp;Just like Baahubali, SS Rajamouli’s upcoming magnum opus is enjoying buzz like anything. Ever since the project was announced with names like Jr NTR, Ram Charan, Ajay Devgn, and Alia Bhatt, the film was said to be a blockbuster. Now, the trailer is out and has already shattered records! But is it worth all the hype? Let’s discuss this in detail.</p>



<p>First of all, get it clear in your mind that SS Rajamouli is a maverick filmmaker. He is known for gifting some visually appealing films that are full of grandeur. But unlike most filmmakers, his work always assures you a high dose of entertainment. So, it’s not only about the big canvas.</p>



<p>Speaking about the trailer (Hindi), RRR takes you back during the British era in India. It starts with a person speaking about a girl one British officer forcibly took away along with him. The girl belongs to the Gond tribe. And there enters our first hero, Jr NTR. He looks heroic, especially when he roars back at a tiger.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_865421"><img src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2021/12/check-out-rrr-trailer-review-starring-jr-ntr-ram-charan-001.jpg" alt="Check Out RRR Trailer Review Starring Jr NTR &amp; Ram Charan" class="wp-image-865421"/><figcaption>( Photo Credit – Still From Trailer )</figcaption></figure>



<p>Jr NTR is a powerful man, fighting against all evils. To stop him, one police officer, a part of the British police force, is appointed. He’s none other than Ram Charan. He too gets his share of the heroic entrance. Interestingly, as the trailer suggests,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/bollywood-news/rrr-heres-why-ram-charan-was-missing-from-the-trailer-launch-event-yesterday/">Ram</a>&nbsp;and NTR share a close friendship, more or less a bond of brotherhood. However, Ram arrests NTR for being a rebel against the British government.</p>



<p>The trailer takes a twist when we witness Ram Charan and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.koimoi.com/south-indian-cinema/rrr-trailer-twitter-reactions-ram-charan-jr-ntr-wow-fans-netizen-writes-we-will-take-revenge-in-gangubai-after-seeing-alia-bhatt/">Jr NTR</a>&nbsp;coming together to take on their enemies.</p>



<p>Apart from the two leading men, the RRR trailer glimpses us with Ajay Devgn’s powerful presence. Unfortunately, we got to see just a little of Alia Bhatt.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image" id="attachment_865424"><img src="https://static-koimoi.akamaized.net/wp-content/new-galleries/2021/12/check-out-rrr-trailer-review-starring-jr-ntr-ram-charan-003.jpg" alt="Check Out RRR Trailer Review Starring Jr NTR &amp; Ram Charan" class="wp-image-865424"/><figcaption>( Photo Credit – Still From Trailer )</figcaption></figure>



<p>Speaking of the SS Rajamouli’s cinematic canvas, in a duration of 3 minutes and 16 seconds, the filmmaker excites us with tremendous sets and VFX work. Especially, the fight shots towards the end look superb. Also, hands down to background music, that holds your attention.</p>



<p>On the whole, the RRR trailer lives up to its hype! Now, keep your calm and wait for January 7, 2022.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/jersey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JavaScript crash course</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[java]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[js]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[webcourse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement No programming knowledge is required. A computer will be useful to take this course! Description Are you]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>No programming knowledge is required. A computer will be useful to take this course!</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p>Are you looking for a way to learn to code but you aren’t sure how or where to start? Maybe you have started learning but feel overwhelmed by the amount of content out there? This course will teach you all the fundamentals of the JavaScript programming language that a beginner should know and it will do so through short but concise examples.</p>



<p>JavaScript is a great language to learn, It is a fun language but also extremely in demand. By taking this course you will kick start your learning process and be on the path to becoming the developer you want to be.</p>



<p>In this course you will be introduced to the very basics of the JavaScript language and the primitive data types, We will then look at Objects, Arrays and functions. You will also be introduced to conditionals and logic. After taking this course you will have a good foundation of all the necessary topics so that you can go off on your own and start to create your own programs.</p>



<p>Whether you are new to programming, New to JavaScript or you just want to build upon some existing knowledge this course will help provide you with a toolbox to becoming a better developer.</p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>Anyone who wants to learn about programming and how to use the JavaScript language</li></ul>



<p>click here : <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://ern.li/OP/iq6kxosl014" target="_blank">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting started with HTML and CSS in 60 minutes</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement Understand english Description Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>Understand english</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p>Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of programming experience in HTML and CSS. I will learn you everything I wish I knew when I first started programming HTML and CSS.</p>



<p>Once you’ve finished this tutorial. You will know every core part of HTML and CSS and you’ve also made your very own portfolio website.</p>



<p>All in all a tutorial to get a good overall understanding about HTML and CSS. After this you will have the knowledge required to create websites on your own.</p>



<p>So if you’re new to HTML and CSS or want to learn more about HTML and CSS this tutorial is for you. We will raise your HTML and CSS skills to the next level!</p>



<p>Hopefully see you in the tutorial, good luck!</p>



<p>Regards,</p>



<p>Jordan Smith</p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>People who have 0 knowledge about HTML and CSS</li></ul>



<p>Show less<a href="https://ern.li/OP/z5kxpkcmaa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tetra’s Creative Guide to Software Testing and Exploration</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sofware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=99</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement Have an open-mind to learn new things or see testing in a different perspective. An interest in]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>Have an open-mind to learn new things or see testing in a different perspective.</li><li>An interest in software testing or software development.</li><li>A passion for embracing automation and a quality first mindset.</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p><strong>TETRA’s (The Entrance To Really Awesome) Creative Guide to Software Testing &amp;&nbsp;Exploration starts here!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Are you a software testing &amp; QA enthusiast? Or a software developer who wants to empower their testing skills? Or none of the above but just want to thrive a career in the field of software engineering &amp; technology?</strong></p>



<p>I believe that thriving in a career in software technology, development, and testing requires&nbsp;<strong>strong testing skills.</strong></p>



<p><strong>By the end of this course, you will be a much stronger software engineer by honing your quality mindset throughout your working career.</strong></p>



<p><strong>This is not another boring software testing guide.</strong></p>



<p>It eliminates much of the dry material in a traditional education or certification for software testing. Your instructor,<strong>&nbsp;Tetra Quality&nbsp;</strong>follows an&nbsp;<strong>unconventional&nbsp;</strong>approach to teaching software testing and QA by focusing on improving your quality mindset through teaching important testing principles.</p>



<p>Learn how to become a strong software tester and team member by learning about&nbsp;<strong>different industry experts</strong>&nbsp;perspectives in the field of software engineering, the 3 tenets of quality, core values of testing, what is exploratory testing, why we do it, and finally, best practices and QA techniques that help guide your software testing to help your organization achieve strong quality software.</p>



<p><strong>Thanks for all the fish!</strong></p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>Anyone with an interest in learning the basics of software testing</li><li>Software Developers, Engineers, and Testers</li><li>Stakeholders in Management, Product, Sales, and Marketing that want to conceptualize, plan, release, and sell high quality products</li></ul>



<p>click here: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://ern.li/OP/ipakxpkojhj" target="_blank">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AWS Solutions Architect Virtual Experience Program</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/about-aws-solutions-architect-virtual-experience-program/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/about-aws-solutions-architect-virtual-experience-program/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 15:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online program]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[architect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aws]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=85</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AWS launch new program ! At AWS, they are eager to give you the chance to start exploring]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>AWS launch new program !</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.coursejoiner.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/image-8-1024x447.png" alt="AWS Solutions Architect Virtual Experience Program free for  students" class="wp-image-98375"/><figcaption>Source: theforage.com</figcaption></figure>



<p>At AWS, they are eager to give you the chance to start exploring what a&nbsp;<strong>career in solutions architecture</strong>&nbsp;could look like for you! They are excited to open up the world of solutions architecture as a role to you and teach you the basics so that you can decide if&nbsp;<strong>solutions architecture</strong>&nbsp;is what you want in your future.&nbsp;</p>



<p>They are also giving you a sneak peek into the&nbsp;<strong>AWS hosting architecture design process</strong>&nbsp;whilst also teaching you the fundamentals of our global company. You’ll familiarize yourself with how our&nbsp;<strong>solution architects&nbsp;</strong>effectively communicate with clients whilst also learning about our billing structures which are key to&nbsp;<strong>providing commercial solutions</strong>&nbsp;for our clients all over the world.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>What’s in it for you?</h2>



<ul><li>Ability to&nbsp;<strong>take our program in your own time, at your own pace</strong>.</li><li><strong>Gain marketable skills and experience</strong>&nbsp;you can build off of.</li><li><strong>Certificate of completion</strong>&nbsp;you can put on your&nbsp;<strong>resume</strong>&nbsp;or your&nbsp;<strong>LinkedIn Profile</strong>&nbsp;to elevate your employability.</li><li>See if a&nbsp;<strong>career in solutions architecture</strong>&nbsp;is the right fit for you!</li></ul>



<h2>Why join this virtual experience program?</h2>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>At AWS, we&#8217;re eager to give you the chance to start exploring what a career in solutions architecture could look like for you! We are excited to open up the world of solutions architecture as a role to you, and teach you the basics so that you can decide if solutions architecture is what you want in your future.&nbsp;</p>



<p>We are giving you a sneak peak into the AWS hosting architecture design process whilst also teaching you the fundamentals of our global company. You&#8217;ll familiarize yourself with how our solution architects effectively communicate with clients whilst also learning about our billing structures which are key to providing commercial solutions for our clients all over the world.&nbsp;</p>



<p>What&#8217;s in it for you:&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>• &nbsp;</strong>Ability to take our program in your own time, at your own pace.<br><strong>•&nbsp;</strong>&nbsp;Gain marketable skills and experience you can build off of.<br><strong>• &nbsp;</strong>Certificate of completion you can put on your resume or your Linkedin to elevate your employability.</p>



<h2>Perks of this Program</h2>



<ul><li><strong>Do it in your own time</strong></li><li><strong>Gain real work Experience</strong></li><li><strong>Make your CV and LinkedIn Profile stand-out</strong></li><li><strong>Learn Direct from AWS</strong></li><li><strong>Discover if this career is for you</strong></li><li><strong>Set yourself for the success</strong></li></ul>



<h2>Certificate</h2>



<p>Yes, you get a free verified Certificate from Amazon AWS. This program is self-paced. It takes 1-2 hours to complete this virtual experience program.</p>



<h3>How to Apply for AWS Solutions Architect Virtual Experience Program?</h3>



<p>To apply for this program&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://www.theforage.com/virtual-internships/prototype/kkE9HyeNcw6rwCRGw/AWS-Solutions-Architect-Virtual-Experience-Program" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CLICK HERE.</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/about-aws-solutions-architect-virtual-experience-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scholarship by Audi !!</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[scholarship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audi scholarship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=66</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hey Students! Are you someone looking for scholarships for higher studies? If yes then today’s post is for]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hey Students! Are you someone looking for scholarships for higher studies? If yes then today’s post is for you as Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship for 2022 has been announced where students starting from 18-30 years are eligible. Your travelling cost will also be managed by the Audi.</p>



<p>To know more who is eligible and minimum qualifications read the post below.</p>



<h2>About Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship 2022</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.coursejoiner.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/image-6-1024x256.png" alt="Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship for 2022" class="wp-image-97915"/></figure>



<p>The Audi Environmental Foundation actively supports research into new technologies and scientific methods for a liveable future. Its stated goal is to make a contribution to environmental protection and to create and promote ways of behaving sustainably.</p>



<p>The Foundation focuses in particular on promoting and developing environmentally compatible technologies, measures for environmental education and protecting the natural necessities of life for humans, animals and plants. It was established in 2009 by AUDI AG as a 100-percent subsidiary and is part of the company’s social and environmental commitment.</p>



<p>Scarce resources, environmental destruction, climate change and population growth – these are just a few aspects that are influencing society, politics and business. With the advancing change in social values, for more and more people, sustainability is becoming part of their outlook on life. The challenges that confront us are increasingly complex. Only by working with partners can we develop good concepts and sound solutions to successfully cope with these challenges.Audi Environmental Foundation is therefore collaborating with One Young World to offer scholarships to 15 inspiring young leaders to attend this year’s One Young World Summit 2022 in Tokyo, Japan.</p>



<h2>What will you get?</h2>



<ul><li>Access to the One Young World Summit 2022 in Tokyo</li><li>Hotel accommodation on a shared basis between 14 and 19 (inclusive) May, 2021</li><li>Participation at the pre-event by Audi AG and the Audi Environmental Foundation on 15 May</li><li>The cost of travel to and from Tokyo (flights in economy)</li><li>Catering which includes breakfast, lunch and dinner</li><li>Transport between the Summit accommodation and the Summit venue</li></ul>



<h2>Eligibility Criteria</h2>



<ul><li>Whose Age falls between 18-30</li><li>Nationals of all countries will be eligible for this scholarship</li><li>Evidenced commitment to delivering positive change</li><li>Demonstrated capacity for leadership</li><li>Understanding of key local and/or global issues</li><li>Track record of generating impactful and innovative solutions</li><li>Demonstrated impact and innovation in tackling environmental challenges.</li></ul>



<p>To apply for this scholarship&nbsp;<a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.oneyoungworld.com/scholarships/audi/2022" target="_blank"><strong>CLICK HERE</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cloud Solutions Architect</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Job]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google help]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[job]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jon in google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=43</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google Remote eligible Apply Note: Google’s hybrid workplace includes remote roles. By applying to this position you will]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Google</li><li>Remote eligible</li><li><a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/signin?jobId=CiUAL2FckXcGxxjZ0yGKW7byU3zZXUvWhxrqPpeeG-fwQsXVkkLaEjsArqK0BfHi5v87cDIqsL0hf89skPApgZU6UYGAG3WQs3klEJIl0qw8noefNH6yDv4TgiBYAWEEN_8kmg%3D%3D_V2&amp;jobTitle=Cloud+Solutions+Architect&amp;loc=US" target="_blank">Apply</a></li></ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/5c12925417002a545a62f5ef-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-45" width="840" height="630"/></figure>



<p>Note: Google’s hybrid workplace includes remote roles. By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following:<br><br><strong>Remote locations: Canada; Quebec, CA.</strong></p>



<h2>Qualifications</h2>



<p>Minimum qualifications:</p>



<ul><li>Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, a related engineering field or equivalent practical experience.</li><li>3 years of experience working with cloud-native application development, container orchestration, Unix/Linux environments, site reliability engineering, developing software systems, and/or software security.</li></ul>



<p>Preferred qualifications:</p>



<ul><li>Master&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, a related engineering field, or equivalent work experience.</li><li>5 years of experience working with a variety of enterprise and cloud technology systems, designing solutions, or developing business applications.</li><li>Experience with deployment and orchestration technologies (e.g., Terraform, Puppet, Chef, Salt, Ansible, Docker, Kubernetes, Mesos, OpenStack, or Jenkins).</li><li>Experience in the business technology market, and expertise working closely with sales and marketing teams in cloud computing or related technical fields.</li><li>Ability to effectively communicate complex technical concepts to a broad range of audiences.</li></ul>



<h2>About the job</h2>



<p>The Google Cloud Platform team helps customers transform and build what&#8217;s next for their business all with technology built in the cloud. Our products are engineered for security, reliability and scalability, running the full stack from infrastructure to applications to devices and hardware. Our teams are dedicated to helping our customers, developers, small and large businesses, educational institutions, and government agencies see the benefits of our technology come to life. As part of an entrepreneurial team in this rapidly growing business, you will play a key role in understanding the needs of our customers and help shape the future of businesses of all sizes use technology to connect with customers, employees, and partners.</p>



<p>As an in-house Cloud Solutions Architect on the Blueprint Solutions team, you will accelerate customers’ onboarding to the cloud by delivering automated open source solutions and tools. You will represent the customer within the Config and Policy Automation team and work closely with product managers and software engineers daily. You will help customers implement best practices for migrating and develop/publish solutions to help modernize their application infrastructure. This includes solutions to help automate, manage, and handle infrastructure. You will provide direction on how to tailor the mechanisms used to secure and deploy workloads reliably and safely to production.</p>



<p>Google Cloud provides organizations with leading infrastructure, platform capabilities and industry solutions. We deliver enterprise-grade cloud solutions that leverage Google’s cutting-edge technology to help companies operate more efficiently and adapt to changing needs, giving customers a foundation for the future. Customers in more than 150 countries turn to Google Cloud as their trusted partner to solve their most critical business problems.</p>



<h2>Responsibilities</h2>



<ul><li>Build and maintain open source template configurations and automated solutions for deploying products on Google Cloud.</li><li>Create and deliver best practices recommendations, tutorials, blog articles, sample code, and technical presentations.</li><li>Partner closely with product managers and engineers to refine our products by collaborating on roadmaps, design documents, and prototypes.</li><li>Facilitate deep technical discussions with customers, partners, and Googlers, and provide customer and market feedback to Product and Engineering teams to help define product direction.</li></ul>



<p>Google is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and is an affirmative action employer. We are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity or Veteran status. We also consider qualified applicants regardless of criminal histories, consistent with legal requirements. See also&nbsp;<a href="https://careers.google.com/eeo/">Google&#8217;s EEO Policy</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://careers.google.com/jobs/dist/legal/OFCCP_EEO_Post.pdf">EEO is the Law.</a>&nbsp;If you have a disability or special need that requires accommodation, please let us know by completing our&nbsp;<a href="https://goo.gl/forms/aBt6Pu71i1kzpLHe2">Accommodations for Applicants form</a>.</p>



<p>To all recruitment agencies: Google does not accept agency resumes. Please do not forward resumes to our jobs alias, Google employees or any other organization location. Google is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.</p>



<p>for apply click here: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/signin?jobId=CiUAL2FckXcGxxjZ0yGKW7byU3zZXUvWhxrqPpeeG-fwQsXVkkLaEjsArqK0BfHi5v87cDIqsL0hf89skPApgZU6UYGAG3WQs3klEJIl0qw8noefNH6yDv4TgiBYAWEEN_8kmg%3D%3D_V2&amp;jobTitle=Cloud+Solutions+Architect&amp;loc=US" target="_blank">Apply</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/cloud-solutions-architect/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marketing: Full-Time Opportunities for MBA Graduates</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/marketing-full-time-opportunities-for-mba-graduates/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/marketing-full-time-opportunities-for-mba-graduates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Job]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MBA graduate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Best opportunity for MBA Graduates Hong Kong, Other, Hong Kong SAR Apply now&#160;&#160;&#160;Save save Marketing: Full-Time Opportunities for]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Best opportunity for MBA Graduates</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/micro.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-39" width="921" height="519"/></figure>



<p>Hong Kong, Other, Hong Kong SAR <a href="javascript:void(0)">Apply now&nbsp;</a>&nbsp;&nbsp;Save save Marketing: Full-Time Opportunities for MBA Graduates to job cart</p>



<ul><li>Job number1226407</li><li>Date posted Dec 24, 2021</li><li>Travel0-25&nbsp;%</li><li>Profession Marketing</li><li>Role type Individual Contributor</li><li>Employment type Full-Time</li></ul>



<p>Every year, we welcome&nbsp;Master of Business Administration&nbsp;(MBA)&nbsp;graduates from every corner of the world to join Microsoft. You bring your aspirations, talent, potential—and excitement for the journey ahead.  &nbsp;</p>



<p> &nbsp;</p>



<p>At Microsoft, our mission is to empower every person and every organization on the planet to achieve more and when you begin your career with us, we empower you through the <a href="https://careers.microsoft.com/students/us/en/microsoft-aspire-experience" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Microsoft Aspire Experience</a>. Those hired into the roles listed below are invited to participate in this two-year learning and development experience where you&#8217;ll build your network, cultivate intentional capabilities and gain perspective into the career opportunities across Microsoft’s many exciting businesses.  &nbsp;</p>



<p> &nbsp;</p>



<p>We’re a company of learn-it-all’s rather than know-it-alls and our culture is centered around embracing a growth mindset, a theme of inspiring excellence, and encouraging teams and leaders to bring their best each day. Does this sound like you? <a href="https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/culture" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn more about our cultural attributes</a>.  &nbsp;</p>



<p> &nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Are you ready to join us and create the future? </strong>Come as you are, do what you love—start your journey with us today! &nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Role Description</strong> &nbsp;</p>



<p>Applications to these opportunities are considered for all available&nbsp;<strong>Marketing&nbsp;</strong>roles, including but not limited to, those described below:&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Responsibilities</h2>



<p><strong>Product Marketing</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Overview</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Product Marketing Manager understands, orchestrates, and influences campaigns and marketing activities, develops integrated marketing campaigns, and delivers product, solutions, and customer campaign feedback to the business. An essential aspect of the role of the Product Marketing Manager is to align the content, timing and delivery of marketing messages and outreach to Microsoft’s customers and partners. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Responsibilities:&nbsp;</p>



<ul><li>Manages plans, forecasts, and resource allocation to align with priorities for business performance and marketing return on investments (ROI).&nbsp;</li><li>Uses business modeling and long-range financial plans to define the strategy for product&nbsp;stock keeping unit (SKU)&nbsp;and pricing.&nbsp;</li></ul>



<ul><li>Drives product and opportunity value by analyzing market opportunity, segmentation and targeting, value proposition and positioning, through strong partnerships with Customer Market Research and Engineering groups.&nbsp;</li><li>Ensures marketing execution, efficacy, and product advocacy by developing integrated marketing plans and driving internal and partner readiness for business return on investment (ROI).&nbsp;</li></ul>



<p><strong>Marketing Communications</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Overview</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Marketing Communication Manager embraces our company’s Marketing principles, is a Microsoft Brand Steward, and drives ongoing improvements in maximizing marketing spend and driving marketing efficiency, and marketing impact. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Responsibilities:&nbsp;</p>



<ul><li>Develops and executes marketing communications strategies, plans, and mixes.&nbsp;</li><li>Contributes insights towards development of a public relations plan for a product line, service, or local market that is focused on specified influential.&nbsp;</li><li>Proposes solutions to or assists in resolution of obstacles that could impact budget, deliverables, or schedule.&nbsp;</li></ul>



<p><strong>Partner/Channel Marketing</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Overview:</strong>&nbsp;</p>



<p>As a Partner/Channel Marketing Manager you will shape the strategy and manage the execution of programs that drive partner profitability. Partner profitability programs accelerate partner cloud practice development by helping the partners build business plans, develop cloud offers, create go-to-market channels, form new business opportunities, increase partner satisfaction, and strengthen partner loyalty.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Responsibilities:&nbsp;</p>



<ul><li>Determines audience needs, preferences, competitive landscape and behavior along the customer or product lifecycle.&nbsp;</li><li>Ensures that marketing plans engage appropriate channel types and capacity to meet business needs.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Implements a part of channel readiness programs that drive sales and technical skills for partners, for successful customer engagement.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Engages with the field to drive program awareness and adoption, and to track engine utilization and effectiveness.&nbsp;</li></ul>



<h2>Qualifications</h2>



<ul><li>Currently pursuing or have completed&nbsp;Master of Business Administration&nbsp;(MBA)&nbsp;degree.&nbsp;</li><li>Demonstrates interest by the continually evolving craft of marketing. &nbsp;</li></ul>



<ul><li>The ability to deliver results in a fast-paced, ambiguous environment. &nbsp;</li><li>Ability to manage complex projects with multiple stakeholders. &nbsp;</li><li>Excellent verbal and written communication, analytical and presentation skills. &nbsp;</li></ul>



<p>Microsoft is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, ancestry, color, family or medical care leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran status, race, religion, sex (including pregnancy), sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws, regulations and ordinances.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Benefits/perks listed below may vary depending on the nature of your employment with Microsoft and the country where you work.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="860" height="430" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Microsoft-is-inviting-applications-for-the-second-batch-of-Virtual-Internship-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-41"/></figure>



<h2>Benefits and Perks</h2>



<ul><li>Industry leading healthcare</li><li>Savings and investments</li><li>Giving programs</li><li>Educational resources</li><li>Maternity and paternity leave</li><li>Opportunities to network and connect</li><li>Discounts on products and services</li><li>Generous time away</li></ul>



<h2>Resources</h2>



<ul><li><a target="_blank" href="https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/accommodationrequest" rel="noreferrer noopener">Accessibility support&nbsp;</a></li><li><a href="https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/faq">Frequently asked questions&nbsp;</a></li><li><a href="https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/interviewtips">Interview tips&nbsp;</a></li><li><a href="https://careers.microsoft.com/students/us/en/search-results">Search more jobs&nbsp;</a></li></ul>



<p>For apply click here: <a href="javascript:void(0)">Apply now </a></p>



<ul class="wp-block-social-links"></ul>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/marketing-full-time-opportunities-for-mba-graduates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TESLA INTERNSHIP</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla internship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=29</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Make a Difference Apply your talents to help secure a cleaner, safer world as a Tesla intern.SEARCH INTERNSHIPS]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Make a Difference</p>



<p>Apply your talents to help secure a cleaner, safer world as a Tesla intern.<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/search/?query=Internship">SEARCH INTERNSHIPS</a></p>



<h2>Real Impact</h2>



<p>Perform meaningful work from day one. We will challenge you to take on high-impact projects, expand your technical skills and exceed your own expectations. We expect interns to perform to the same level of excellence as our full-time employees—which is why we often hire them back.</p>



<h4>“Tesla internships are exceptional because you are treated as a full‑time employee for three months. I felt empowered to make a change.”</h4>



<h5>Kate P.</h5>



<p>Former Autopilot Computer Vision Intern<br>Current Staff&nbsp;AI Product Manager</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/aishwarya-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-31"/></figure>



<h4>“A Tesla internship is best summarized by cool projects, high levels of responsibility, an incredible community of coworkers and unparalleled opportunities for personal growth.”</h4>



<h5>Aishwarya V.</h5>



<p>Former Mechanical Engineering Intern<br>Current Mechanical Engineer</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/kate-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-30"/></figure>



<h4>“Tesla employees are just a bunch of nerds who love working on exciting products. As an intern, you can talk to anyone at the company, and they’ll be happy to share what they’re working on, and why it’s cool and challenging.”</h4>



<h5>Jake E.</h5>



<p>Former Test Engineering Intern<br>Current Senior Test Engineer</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/jake-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-32"/></figure>



<h2>An Inclusive Network</h2>



<p>Experience one-on-one mentorship, interactive networking events and weekly seminars within our exceptional community of experts. Tesla interns collaborate across disciplines, borders and production lines to support our shared mission of accelerating the world’s transition to sustainable energy.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="864" height="488" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/resources.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-33"/></figure>



<h4>Resources</h4>



<p><a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/intern-resources">Learn more</a>&nbsp;about applying, preparing for the technical interview and refining your resume.</p>



<h4>Frequently Asked Questions</h4>



<p><a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/intern-resources#faq">Learn more</a>&nbsp;about our selection process, timeline and eligibility&nbsp;requirements.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="864" height="488" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/faqs.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-34"/></figure>



<h2>Join Us</h2>



<p>Accelerate the world’s transition to sustainable energy<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/search/?query=Internship">SEARCH INTERNSHIPS</a></p>



<p>Tesla participates in the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/e-verify?redirect=no" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">E-Verify Program</a>.</p>



<p>Tesla is an Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action employer committed to diversity in the workplace. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, age, national origin, disability, protected veteran status, gender identity or any other factor protected by applicable federal, state or local laws.</p>



<p>Tesla is also committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. Please let your recruiter know if you need an accommodation at any point during the interview process.</p>



<p>For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site,&nbsp;<a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/screen-reader/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">download a free compatible screen reader</a>&nbsp;(<a href="https://support.google.com/chromebook/answer/7031755" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">view the free step-by-step tutorial</a>).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>INFOSYS INTERNSHIP</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infosys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infosys Internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[intern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[job]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hey learners! Are you looking for some project based Internship then Infosys Springboard is for you. Infosys Springboard]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hey learners! Are you looking for some project based Internship then Infosys Springboard is for you. Infosys Springboard Offering Project Internship is for fresher who wants to learn the new technology . In this Program you will assign to variety of internship and you need to make the teams to complete the internship .</p>



<p>To know more about this read the blog post below.</p>



<h2>About Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship Program</h2>



<p>The Infosys Springboard internship program is an excellent learning opportunity for students/learners who are aspiring professionals to hone their existing skills and transition to global corporate professionals.</p>



<p>Applicants must complete all the courses prescribed in the learning path for the project and score 60% or above in the self-assessment present in the courses.</p>



<p>They must pass the certifications if any prescribed in the learning path for the project. Here are the learning paths for the pre-requisite learning.</p>



<h2>Eligibility Criteria</h2>



<ul><li>Applicants must have passed 12th Standard or equivalent or higher examination from a recognized Board or University and must be pursuing graduation or completed graduation/post-graduation</li><li>Applicants must complete all the courses prescribed in the pre-requisite learning microsite for the project and score 60% or above in self-assessment present at the end of the course</li><li>They must pass the certification(s) if prescribed in the pre-requisite learning microsite</li><li>They must submit responses to a survey which will be activated when they click on the ‘Apply’ button</li></ul>



<h2>Selection criteria</h2>



<ul><li>The internship with Infosys Springboard will have limited seats</li><li>The following are the guidelines(not limited to) for selection to the program:<ul><li>Completion of courses in the pre-requisite learning microsite and performance in the self-assessments</li><li>Completion of certifications(if any) and performance in them</li><li>Survey responses</li><li>Performance in the interviews with mentors</li><li>Performance in a qualification exam if Infosys decides to conduct one</li><li>The decision of Infosys will be final for selection of interns</li></ul></li></ul>



<h2>Internship Timeline</h2>



<p><strong>Dec 24, 2021</strong></p>



<ul><li>Infosys Springboard Internship opens</li></ul>



<p><strong>Dec 24, 2021 – Jan 14, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Browse for open projects and explore</li><li>Apply for project that suits</li><li>Complete the pre-requisite learning courses and certification(if any)</li><li>Prepare for interview by Project Mentors(if invited)</li></ul>



<p><strong>Jan 17 – 28, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Attend interviews as per shared schedule</li><li>Allocation of project(if selected)</li></ul>



<p><strong>Feb – Apr, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Interact with Project Mentors</li><li>Design, code and test the solution</li><li>Deploy and integrate</li></ul>



<p><strong>Mar – Apr, 2022</strong></p>



<ul><li>Project milestone and evaluations</li></ul>



<h2>List of Projects and other details</h2>



<p>1 : EasyQ – AI Based question &amp; answer generation tool</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL</li><li>Event Intern</li></ul>



<p>2. Event Management</p>



<ul><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>3. GAN for CVD</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: AI and ML</li></ul>



<p>4. HONQPGen – AI Based question hands on generation tool</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Artificial Intelligence Team</li><li>Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Artificial Intelligence</li></ul>



<p>5. InfyDataQ – From Messy to Clean Data</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Open systems</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: LAMP</li></ul>



<p>6. InfyKiddoFun – Making Learning Fun!Theme: Digital Learning</p>



<ul><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, .NET</li></ul>



<p>7. Linux Enterprise Lab – A hands-on experience!</p>



<ul><li>Theme: System Administration</li><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 10 weeks</li><li>Technology: CentOS Everything iso, Ngnix binary</li></ul>



<p>8. Market analyst</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 2</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>9. MeridianPlatform – Outlook plugin integration</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Remote team collaboration</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 10 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL</li></ul>



<p>10. QuestBank – To create a treasure trove of questions for assessments</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Digital Learning</li><li>Team Size: 5</li><li>Estimated Time: 12 weeks</li><li>Technology: Angular, .NET</li></ul>



<p>11. Brand Management Intern</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 4</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<p>12. Content Marketing Intern</p>



<ul><li>Theme: Content Marketing</li><li>Team Size: 2</li><li>Estimated Time: 8 weeks</li><li>Technology: N/A</li></ul>



<h3>How to Apply for Infosys Springboard Project Based Internship Program?</h3>



<p>To apply in this Internship&nbsp;<a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://infyspringboard.onwingspan.com/en/page/embed-internship" target="_blank">CLICK HERE</a></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/11/28/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
