<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>website &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/tag/website/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 06:00:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>JavaScript crash course</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[java]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[javascript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[js]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[webcourse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement No programming knowledge is required. A computer will be useful to take this course! Description Are you]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>No programming knowledge is required. A computer will be useful to take this course!</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p>Are you looking for a way to learn to code but you aren’t sure how or where to start? Maybe you have started learning but feel overwhelmed by the amount of content out there? This course will teach you all the fundamentals of the JavaScript programming language that a beginner should know and it will do so through short but concise examples.</p>



<p>JavaScript is a great language to learn, It is a fun language but also extremely in demand. By taking this course you will kick start your learning process and be on the path to becoming the developer you want to be.</p>



<p>In this course you will be introduced to the very basics of the JavaScript language and the primitive data types, We will then look at Objects, Arrays and functions. You will also be introduced to conditionals and logic. After taking this course you will have a good foundation of all the necessary topics so that you can go off on your own and start to create your own programs.</p>



<p>Whether you are new to programming, New to JavaScript or you just want to build upon some existing knowledge this course will help provide you with a toolbox to becoming a better developer.</p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>Anyone who wants to learn about programming and how to use the JavaScript language</li></ul>



<p>click here : <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://ern.li/OP/iq6kxosl014" target="_blank">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/javascript-crash-course/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting started with HTML and CSS in 60 minutes</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement Understand english Description Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>Understand english</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p>Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of programming experience in HTML and CSS. I will learn you everything I wish I knew when I first started programming HTML and CSS.</p>



<p>Once you’ve finished this tutorial. You will know every core part of HTML and CSS and you’ve also made your very own portfolio website.</p>



<p>All in all a tutorial to get a good overall understanding about HTML and CSS. After this you will have the knowledge required to create websites on your own.</p>



<p>So if you’re new to HTML and CSS or want to learn more about HTML and CSS this tutorial is for you. We will raise your HTML and CSS skills to the next level!</p>



<p>Hopefully see you in the tutorial, good luck!</p>



<p>Regards,</p>



<p>Jordan Smith</p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>People who have 0 knowledge about HTML and CSS</li></ul>



<p>Show less<a href="https://ern.li/OP/z5kxpkcmaa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
