<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tesla &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/tag/tesla/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:18:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>TESLA INTERNSHIP</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla internship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=29</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Make a Difference Apply your talents to help secure a cleaner, safer world as a Tesla intern.SEARCH INTERNSHIPS Real Impact Perform meaningful work from day one. We will challenge you to take on high-impact projects, expand your technical skills and exceed your own expectations. We expect interns to perform to the same level of excellence [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Make a Difference</p>



<p>Apply your talents to help secure a cleaner, safer world as a Tesla intern.<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/search/?query=Internship">SEARCH INTERNSHIPS</a></p>



<h2>Real Impact</h2>



<p>Perform meaningful work from day one. We will challenge you to take on high-impact projects, expand your technical skills and exceed your own expectations. We expect interns to perform to the same level of excellence as our full-time employees—which is why we often hire them back.</p>



<h4>“Tesla internships are exceptional because you are treated as a full‑time employee for three months. I felt empowered to make a change.”</h4>



<h5>Kate P.</h5>



<p>Former Autopilot Computer Vision Intern<br>Current Staff&nbsp;AI Product Manager</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/aishwarya-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-31"/></figure>



<h4>“A Tesla internship is best summarized by cool projects, high levels of responsibility, an incredible community of coworkers and unparalleled opportunities for personal growth.”</h4>



<h5>Aishwarya V.</h5>



<p>Former Mechanical Engineering Intern<br>Current Mechanical Engineer</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/kate-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-30"/></figure>



<h4>“Tesla employees are just a bunch of nerds who love working on exciting products. As an intern, you can talk to anyone at the company, and they’ll be happy to share what they’re working on, and why it’s cool and challenging.”</h4>



<h5>Jake E.</h5>



<p>Former Test Engineering Intern<br>Current Senior Test Engineer</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="1320" height="804" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/jake-intern.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-32"/></figure>



<h2>An Inclusive Network</h2>



<p>Experience one-on-one mentorship, interactive networking events and weekly seminars within our exceptional community of experts. Tesla interns collaborate across disciplines, borders and production lines to support our shared mission of accelerating the world’s transition to sustainable energy.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="864" height="488" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/resources.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-33"/></figure>



<h4>Resources</h4>



<p><a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/intern-resources">Learn more</a>&nbsp;about applying, preparing for the technical interview and refining your resume.</p>



<h4>Frequently Asked Questions</h4>



<p><a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/intern-resources#faq">Learn more</a>&nbsp;about our selection process, timeline and eligibility&nbsp;requirements.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="864" height="488" src="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/faqs.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-34"/></figure>



<h2>Join Us</h2>



<p>Accelerate the world’s transition to sustainable energy<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/search/?query=Internship">SEARCH INTERNSHIPS</a></p>



<p>Tesla participates in the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tesla.com/careers/e-verify?redirect=no" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">E-Verify Program</a>.</p>



<p>Tesla is an Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action employer committed to diversity in the workplace. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, age, national origin, disability, protected veteran status, gender identity or any other factor protected by applicable federal, state or local laws.</p>



<p>Tesla is also committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. Please let your recruiter know if you need an accommodation at any point during the interview process.</p>



<p>For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site,&nbsp;<a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/screen-reader/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">download a free compatible screen reader</a>&nbsp;(<a href="https://support.google.com/chromebook/answer/7031755" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">view the free step-by-step tutorial</a>).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/26/tesla-internship/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
