<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>scholarship &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo/tag/scholarship/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Scholarship by Audi !!</title>
		<link>https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/</link>
					<comments>https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[scholarship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audi scholarship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo/?p=66</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hey Students! Are you someone looking for scholarships for higher studies? If yes then today’s post is for]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hey Students! Are you someone looking for scholarships for higher studies? If yes then today’s post is for you as Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship for 2022 has been announced where students starting from 18-30 years are eligible. Your travelling cost will also be managed by the Audi.</p>



<p>To know more who is eligible and minimum qualifications read the post below.</p>



<h2>About Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship 2022</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.coursejoiner.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/image-6-1024x256.png" alt="Audi Environmental Foundation Scholarship for 2022" class="wp-image-97915"/></figure>



<p>The Audi Environmental Foundation actively supports research into new technologies and scientific methods for a liveable future. Its stated goal is to make a contribution to environmental protection and to create and promote ways of behaving sustainably.</p>



<p>The Foundation focuses in particular on promoting and developing environmentally compatible technologies, measures for environmental education and protecting the natural necessities of life for humans, animals and plants. It was established in 2009 by AUDI AG as a 100-percent subsidiary and is part of the company’s social and environmental commitment.</p>



<p>Scarce resources, environmental destruction, climate change and population growth – these are just a few aspects that are influencing society, politics and business. With the advancing change in social values, for more and more people, sustainability is becoming part of their outlook on life. The challenges that confront us are increasingly complex. Only by working with partners can we develop good concepts and sound solutions to successfully cope with these challenges.Audi Environmental Foundation is therefore collaborating with One Young World to offer scholarships to 15 inspiring young leaders to attend this year’s One Young World Summit 2022 in Tokyo, Japan.</p>



<h2>What will you get?</h2>



<ul><li>Access to the One Young World Summit 2022 in Tokyo</li><li>Hotel accommodation on a shared basis between 14 and 19 (inclusive) May, 2021</li><li>Participation at the pre-event by Audi AG and the Audi Environmental Foundation on 15 May</li><li>The cost of travel to and from Tokyo (flights in economy)</li><li>Catering which includes breakfast, lunch and dinner</li><li>Transport between the Summit accommodation and the Summit venue</li></ul>



<h2>Eligibility Criteria</h2>



<ul><li>Whose Age falls between 18-30</li><li>Nationals of all countries will be eligible for this scholarship</li><li>Evidenced commitment to delivering positive change</li><li>Demonstrated capacity for leadership</li><li>Understanding of key local and/or global issues</li><li>Track record of generating impactful and innovative solutions</li><li>Demonstrated impact and innovation in tackling environmental challenges.</li></ul>



<p>To apply for this scholarship&nbsp;<a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.oneyoungworld.com/scholarships/audi/2022" target="_blank"><strong>CLICK HERE</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://TheInfo.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/27/scholarship-by-audi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
