<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>course &#8211; TheInfo</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/tag/course/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:37:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Getting started with HTML and CSS in 60 minutes</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement Understand english Description Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of programming experience in HTML and CSS. I will learn you everything I wish I knew when I first started programming HTML and CSS. Once you’ve finished this tutorial. You will know every core part of HTML and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>Understand english</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p>Welcome to this tutorial. My name is Jordan Smith and I’ve 8 years of programming experience in HTML and CSS. I will learn you everything I wish I knew when I first started programming HTML and CSS.</p>



<p>Once you’ve finished this tutorial. You will know every core part of HTML and CSS and you’ve also made your very own portfolio website.</p>



<p>All in all a tutorial to get a good overall understanding about HTML and CSS. After this you will have the knowledge required to create websites on your own.</p>



<p>So if you’re new to HTML and CSS or want to learn more about HTML and CSS this tutorial is for you. We will raise your HTML and CSS skills to the next level!</p>



<p>Hopefully see you in the tutorial, good luck!</p>



<p>Regards,</p>



<p>Jordan Smith</p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>People who have 0 knowledge about HTML and CSS</li></ul>



<p>Show less<a href="https://ern.li/OP/z5kxpkcmaa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/getting-started-with-html-and-css-in-60-minutes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tetra’s Creative Guide to Software Testing and Exploration</title>
		<link>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/</link>
					<comments>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sofware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[udemy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/?p=99</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Requirement Have an open-mind to learn new things or see testing in a different perspective. An interest in software testing or software development. A passion for embracing automation and a quality first mindset. Description TETRA’s (The Entrance To Really Awesome) Creative Guide to Software Testing &#38;&#160;Exploration starts here! Are you a software testing &#38; QA [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Requirement</strong></p>



<ul><li>Have an open-mind to learn new things or see testing in a different perspective.</li><li>An interest in software testing or software development.</li><li>A passion for embracing automation and a quality first mindset.</li></ul>



<h2>Description</h2>



<p><strong>TETRA’s (The Entrance To Really Awesome) Creative Guide to Software Testing &amp;&nbsp;Exploration starts here!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Are you a software testing &amp; QA enthusiast? Or a software developer who wants to empower their testing skills? Or none of the above but just want to thrive a career in the field of software engineering &amp; technology?</strong></p>



<p>I believe that thriving in a career in software technology, development, and testing requires&nbsp;<strong>strong testing skills.</strong></p>



<p><strong>By the end of this course, you will be a much stronger software engineer by honing your quality mindset throughout your working career.</strong></p>



<p><strong>This is not another boring software testing guide.</strong></p>



<p>It eliminates much of the dry material in a traditional education or certification for software testing. Your instructor,<strong>&nbsp;Tetra Quality&nbsp;</strong>follows an&nbsp;<strong>unconventional&nbsp;</strong>approach to teaching software testing and QA by focusing on improving your quality mindset through teaching important testing principles.</p>



<p>Learn how to become a strong software tester and team member by learning about&nbsp;<strong>different industry experts</strong>&nbsp;perspectives in the field of software engineering, the 3 tenets of quality, core values of testing, what is exploratory testing, why we do it, and finally, best practices and QA techniques that help guide your software testing to help your organization achieve strong quality software.</p>



<p><strong>Thanks for all the fish!</strong></p>



<h2>Who this course is for:</h2>



<ul><li>Anyone with an interest in learning the basics of software testing</li><li>Software Developers, Engineers, and Testers</li><li>Stakeholders in Management, Product, Sales, and Marketing that want to conceptualize, plan, release, and sell high quality products</li></ul>



<p>click here: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://ern.li/OP/ipakxpkojhj" target="_blank">Enroll Now</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ravi-parihar1.github.io/TheInfo/2021/12/28/tetras-creative-guide-to-software-testing-and-exploration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
